Wealth, Fame, Power.
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer,
and his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it.
These words lured men to
the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine.
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era.
Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for.
One Piece.
Compass left behind,
it'll only slow us down.
Your heart will be your guide,
raise the sails and take the helm.
That legendary place that
the end of the map reveals.
Is only legendary till
someone proves it real?
Through it all, through
all the trouble of times!
Through the heartache
and through the pain.
Know that I will be there to stand by you.
Just like I know you'll stand by me.
So come aboard and bring along
All your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything
That we're looking for?
There's always room for you!
If you wanna be my friend.
We are, we are on a cruise!
We are
Oh, so hungry.
When the hell are we going
to reach land, anyway?
Who knows?
We're just sailing on the wind and
the waves, going where they take us.
Don't you find it dumb that
someone trying to be king
of the pirates doesn't have
a single navigational skill?
Not really.
I just drift around.
What about you?
Aren't you some famous bounty
hunter who sailed the seas?
I don't have any recollection of
ever calling myself a bounty hunter.
I set out onto the open sea
in search of just one man,
but then I couldn't
get back to my village.
By that point, I had no choice but to
go after pirate ships to earn a living.
Oh, I see.
So you're just lost.
Hey, don't let it like that!
Heh heh, another big haul today.
That's two in a row.
All of this should keep Buggy
from getting too mad at us.
Hey, what's with that boat out there?
We should check it out.
Oh, it's a lady.
Hey, wake up, little girl.
Please tell me i'm not dreaming this time?
Finding help out here in
the middle of nowhere.
If you're real, then please.
Could you get me some water?
I'm so thirsty.
I'll give you as much jewelry
and valuables as you like!
If you could just give
me one little drink?
No sweat, we'll help you.
But not until we see what kind
of treasure you're holding on to.
Yeah, don't mind us, we'll just be a man.
I can't get the damn thing open.
Okay, hold up, here we go.
If you want, you can keep the whole thing.
It's not my style.
But that's our boat!
You tricked us!
From the look of those clouds
moving in from the south,
I'd say a cold front's coming.
So you can probably expect strong
winds and squalls any time now, really.
Also, in that small boat, and you
run a bit of a chance of capsizing.
Bingo!
See ya!
I'll just take whatever
treasure you guys got here!
Get back here, you bitch!
I'll get you for this!
Ugh, I am so hungry.
It's killing me.
Hey, look, a bird. I
know! Let's eat it! Huh?
How do we catch it?
Leave that to me!
GUM-GUM-PROCKET!
Makes sense.
You moron!
What the hell's going on now?
Hey!
You there!
Stop!
Please!
Man overboard!
Stop!
I can't believe I find
shipwreckers at a time like this!
I can't stop!
You're just gonna have to jump in!
What?!
I'm actually impressed
you made it on board!
Are you trying to kill us?!
Stop the boat now!
The three of us are members of
Back the Clown's pirate crew!
This boat is ours now!
Huh?
I'm sorry, we had no idea you were
the famous pirate hunter Zoro.
Please forgive us.
Thanks to you three idiots,
I lost sight of my friend.
So just keep paddling. Yes, sir.
Knowing Luffy, he'll probably pull
off something once he spots land.
So, any ideas about what we do now?
Good question.
If Captain Buggy finds out a girl stole
our boat and our treasure, we're history.
I know. Huh?
So who is this Buggy guy?
You've never heard of Buggy the Clown?
Nope.
He's the ruthless captain
of our pirate ship.
And he's eaten one of the devil fruits.
But above everything else, he
is one truly terrifying man.
Yes I finally got it.
Hey girl, get back here!
You better give us that map back or else
we just stole that chart of the Grand Line.
It belongs to us!
Damn it!
If we don't get that
thing back then we're...
You're as good as dead.
We'll be killed by one of
the captain's cannonballs!
Captain Buggy!
I spotted something high
in the sky above the pond!
Well, shoot it down!
What's that?
What was that?
What the hell?
A guy fell from the sky.
Dammit, why were there
cannonballs flying at me?
At least I'm safe now.
And what just happened to me was awesome.
Geez, I'm so hungry.
Oh, hey boss, thanks for
coming to save me. Huh?
Who are you?
They're all yours now, boss! Have fun!
Hey, that girl's getting away!
That's okay, we've got her boss now.
You're in trouble, kid.
You should've let your
crony fit for herself.
You guys know of anywhere
good to eat around here?
Food's the least of your worries now!
You better keep your hands
off my hat you bastard
i wonder if they've
killed that poor guy yet
wow you're really strong
even though both of them had sabers
you beat them barehanded Hey,
you're the girl who set me up.
Who are you?
I'm a talented thief who
steals strictly from pirates.
The name's Nami.
Hey, want to team up with me?
Um, thanks anyway, lady,
but I think I'll pass.
Hold on!
At least think about it first!
You're telling me they still
haven't caught the thief?
Uh, not yet, but...
But they should be in pursuit.
Right now, Captain, sir.
Now explain to me, how in the world did
she manage to get her hands on that chart?
Huh?
If we're preparing to enter the
Grand Line and go on a rampage,
then why wasn't the
chart properly guarded?
I don't know, sir.
The map was just sitting out,
plain as the nose on your face.
What did you say?
I mean, it was easy for
her to find and take it.
Did you hear something about my nose?
Sir, are you trying to tell
me you find my nose funny?
Is my nose amusing?
No sir, you misunderstood!
Oh no, you were quite clear!
Help me!
This isn't good!
He's gonna use the Devil Fruit power!
Tell me, who am I?
Captain...
And what happens if someone defies me?
Flashy...
Death...
Await...
Them...
Please...
Forgive me...
Quit your groveling.
I'll overlook your slip-up
and forgive you this time.
But you better get that chart back.
Don't screw up again, or else.
Yes, Captain Buggy!
Yum.
So, do you live in this
big house all by yourself?
This isn't my house.
I'm just staying here for the time being.
Everyone's left this town
because of Captain Buggy.
So you're just a petty thief. How rude.
I only steal from people
who deserve it. Pirates.
So don't compare me to
some scumbag petty thief.
The thief's a thief as
far as I'm concerned.
My goal is to earn a
hundred million berries,
no matter how hard it
is or how long it takes.
What do you need so
many berries for anyway?
It's a secret.
But with this chart of the Grand Line,
the hundred million is now
a definite possibility.
A chart?
So you must be a navigator.
I'm the most skilled navigator
you're ever likely to meet.
Oh wow, that's perfect!
Then how about you join my crew?
I've been looking to recruit a navigator.
Really? Sure.
You can be our newest crew member.
No.
I suppose this means
you're a pirate. Yeah.
I made a solemn promise.
I promised the guy who
gave me this hat that I'd
form a crew and become
the greatest pirate ever.
There's nothing in this world
that I despise more than pirates.
I only like money and tangerines. Come on.
Be our navigator. I said no.
You're lost.
Did you find her or what?
No, I can't find her anywhere.
Where could she be hiding?
I don't know, but we're going to be in big
trouble if we don't get that chart back.
I got to do something about them.
I guess I might consider joining you,
but only if you'll agree
to certain conditions.
Really?
I'll do anything.
Well, then I want you to come with me to
pay a little visit to Buggy the Pirate.
But first...
Why did you have to tie me up?
The rope's just for appearances.
Well, okay, then.
I've been looking forward to meeting
some other pirates, so let's get going.
Just hold your horses.
What's the big rush?
What?
Are you telling me the thief got away?
Please forgive us, Captain Buggy.
I've never seen a more
pathetic group than you three.
Time to die!
Captain Buggy, I have news!
What is it?
The girl who stole our chart is back.
And with a prisoner.
What?
It's her!
That's the sneaky thief
who stole the chart!
I've captured the thief,
Captain Buggy the Clown.
And here's your chart back.
Not that I don't appreciate it, but why
the sudden change of heart, little girl?
I had another fight with my boss,
and I just can't take it anymore.
So I thought I'd see if
I could join your crew.
You're fed up, huh?
I must admit you're an amusing girl.
I like you.
Of course you can join my crew.
I've successfully infiltrated them.
Pirates are so dumb
and easy to manipulate.
Hey, guys, why am I in a cage?
It's a great day to be a pilot.
Girl, what do you call yourself? I'm Nami.
Then let's have a welcome
party for our new friend Nami.
Let's celebrate!
What's wrong?
We're throwing this party
in your honor, so eat up!
Thanks for the party, Captain Buggy.
I'll just keep my eyes peeled for
a chance to take back that chart.
Maybe I'll swipe all of Buggy's
treasure, too, while I'm at it.
Ah! Damn it!
This is such a flashy party.
Now listen up!
Men, it's time to prepare the buggy ball!
All set, Captain.
What are you doing with that thing?
Just observe the awesome might
of the buggy ball. Light it.
That was one heck of an explosion.
It looked like it was one of the
captain's beloved buggy balls.
Buggy balls?
That was flashy.
With these buggy balls
and my Devil Fruit powers,
I should have no problem
conquering the Grand Line.
Right, Nami? Right! Yes, of course! Huh?
But it's my destiny to
conquer the Grand Line!
And then I'm gonna become
King of the Pirates!
Shut up, idiot!
I can see why you're sick
of him, Nami! Yeah, I know.
He never takes anything seriously,
thinks that life's a big game.
He acts like a little kid!
I see.
Then how about I give you a buggy
ball to blow away your old boss?
It'll be a great opportunity for you to
prove your loyalty to me, your new captain.
Men?
That's alright, Captain.
We don't have to finish him off quite yet.
Let's get back to the welcoming
party and just have more fun.
This is my idea of having more fun!
If I don't shoot, I'll be killed.
But if I do shoot, then I'm
no better than these pirates.
Fire!
Now!
Light the fuse, Nami!
You're not whipping out on me, are you?
FIRE! FIRE! FIRE!
What's the matter?
Your hands are shaking.
FIRE! FIRE!
That's what happens when you take
on pirates with half-ass resolve.
FIRE! FIRE! Resolve? To do what?
To kill someone like it's nothing?
Is that a pirate's resolve? No.
FIRE! FIRE! FIRE!
You've got to be willing
to risk your own life.
Here, new chick.
Quit being such a tease.
Let me show you how to light the cannon.
My mistake! Sorry!
Nami!
What's the meaning of this outrage?
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
Just shoot him already!
Huh.
So, now you've decided to save me?
Don't be so stupid!
I'm not doing this for you, you idiot!
I just don't want to lower myself to
the level of these inhuman pirates!
Okay, thanks anyway.
Pirates took the life of
a person very dear to me.
I'll never be one of them!
Oh, I see.
Nabi, the fuse!
So you think pirates are just
inhuman filth, is that right?
Get her, man!
Water, water, water, water, water.
Not good.
Whoa!
Watch out!
Hey, now.
It's not very nice of you guns
to gang up on a poor girl.
Zoro!
You hurt?
I said, are you hurt?
No, I'm fine, I think.
Phew, what a relief.
I'm glad you found us.
Now hurry up and come get me out of here.
How do you keep getting
yourself into these situations?
First a bird flies off with you, and
now I find you trapped in a cage.
It's an interesting story, actually.
That's, yeah, that little
brat just called him Zoro.
The crew he mentioned earlier
was the pirate hunter Zoro?
What's going on here?
So you're Zoro.
If you're here for my head, you've
got quite a struggle before you.
No, not interested.
I gave up pirate hunting.
I'm here for my friend.
But I'm interested, though.
Killing you would boast to my reputation.
If you try, you'll die.
I tried to warn you, but oh well
That wasn't much of a
fight, now was it? Oh, wow!
He's weak!
Way to go, Zoro! No way!
Hey, why are they laughing?
Their captain is lying dead on the
ground and yet they're still laughing?
What's going on?
Fellas, what do you find so damn funny?
Zoro!
Bucky's still alive!
What the hell?
The chop-chop fruit.
That's the name of the devil
fruit that's given me my powers.
I'm a chop-chop person, and now I
can never be defeated by the sword!
His limbs re-attach?
And I always thought that the devil fruits
were just a story that pirates told.
So he's a chop-chop man?
That's pretty freaky.
I didn't hit any vital organs, but
that's a serious wound you have there,
so I'm guessing that I am the winner!
Oh, crap!
The tables have turned!
If we don't do something quick,
they're gonna kill all three of us!
I let my guard down.
Stupid mistake.
Buggy! Buggy! Buggy!
Stabbing him in the back was
a cowardly move, you big nose!
You idiot!
Don't call him that!
What are you doing?
What's that?
You said?
I got a big nose!
Luffy!
Buggy!
I'M GONNA KICK YOUR ASS SOON
AS I GET OUT OF THIS CAGE!
YOU KICK MY ASS?
YOU 'VE GOT A LOT OF NERVE, KID!
NOW I'M AFRAID ALL THREE OF YOU
ARE GOING TO DIE HERE TODAY!
BY MY OWN HAND!
SO IF YOU'RE GOING TO DO ANY ASS
KICKING, YOU BETTER DO IT SOON!
WE'RE DONE FOR, IT'S ALL OVER!
I refuse to die!
Zoro, get up! What?
You better have a really good
plan or else we're all dead!
So what are you guys gonna do?
I got you.
Nothing makes sense anymore.
This is why I hate pirates!
You're a fool!
Time to die!
Your three-sword style has no effect
on me, I already told you. I ne...
Hey!
Listen what I'm talking to you!
No! Crap!
The cannon's pointed at us! No!
Hurry! Light it!
Huh? Do it now! Right! Wait! Just wait!
The cannon's still loaded
with a special buckyball!
I don't wanna go out like this!
Shut in by my own balls!
I can't believe you just did
that, you ungrateful little girl!
Wait! No! Stop!
Stop it now!
You okay, Zoro?
How bad are you injured?
Just shut up and don't
worry about how I'm doing.
I need to concentrate if I'm
going to get us out of this.
Who is this guy?
Hey, Luffy. Who's this?
Who's the girl? Oh, right.
She's our new navigator.
I'm not so sure about that.
Who are you guys, anyway?
Move.
You're in the way.
I guess even a lowly pirate
can still rescue his friend.
As a kid, I never stopped.
Searching for a great treasure!
I had a map in my mind.
That I knew would lead me.
I had to find my way to that place!
Before someone could beat me.
The promised land was in my
grasp, and I wouldn't let go!
I won't stop chasing
it until it comes true!
But if the world ever
changes, I call out your name!
We return to the time when
everything's the same.
As long as I'm with you,
my memories won't fade.
Waiting for that one true dream?